

Contact

- **(**+34) 638 318 200
- angel1995.6@gmail.com
- Carrer de Joan Bautista Torroella i Bastons, 1, 1-1 17003 Girona, Spain
- in www.linkedin.com/in/ angelmartinezcampos
- CV ONLINE angelmartinezcampos.github.io

Expertise

- VHDL/Verilog
- SoC / SoPC
- Python/R
- FPGA
- C/C++
- uControlers
- AWS
- Vivado/Vitis
- SOI
- Altium Design
- QLIK/PowerBI
- Multissim &
- Rash
- Iltihoard
- Git
- Matlab/Labview
- Jupyter
- Google Colab

Languages

Spanish
Catalan
English
French

Mother Tongue
Mother Tongue
A1

ANGEL MARTÍNEZ CAMPOS

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

About Me

Electronic engineer with a master's degree in electronics and over 5 years of international experience as a software engineer. My goal is to build a career focused on embedded systems and artificial intelligence. My skills include adaptability, effective decision-making in critical situations, a continuous thirst for learning, creativity, organizational abilities, and strong teamwork capabilities.

Experience

SIEMENS RAIL AUTOMATION | 2019 - currently | Madrid, Spain

Digital Service Engineer

Designing digital Cloud or OnPremises solutions focused on railway products. Defining the architecture and structure spanning from the back-end to the frontend including all the ETL process of the onboard & railway infrastructure data.

Service Engineer

Analysing, correcting failures and designing of the embedded systems in international projects in railway sector. Purposing HW and SW solutions at R&D to improve the system and remove the failures. Test in situ the proposals and problem solving on the project location if needed.

IMTECH BELGIUM | 2018 - 2019 | Antwerp, Belgium Engineer Software Junior

Working an automation engineer with expertise in PLCs, focusing on the automotive industry. Contributing in the production lines automation at companies like Volvo and Audi. Improving efficiency, reducing downtime, and enhancing security in production lines through robust automation solutions.

TECNO-ELÈCTRIC GIRONA | 2017 - 2018 | Girona, Spain Engineer Software Junior

I was involved in the creation of cabinets and wiring systems for automated industrial processes. This entailed fabricating and assembling cabinets, meticulously crafting wiring harnesses, and integrating PLCs and other components.

J.COLL ENGINYERIA | 2016 - 2017 | Figueres, Spain *Technical Office Engineer*

CAD designing electrical installations and fire protection projects, ensuring safety and efficiency. Creating compliant solutions for industrial facilities, providing indepth knowledge of regulations and standards.

Education

M.Sc. Industrial Electronics

Universidad Politécnica de Madrid 2021 Master's Thesis: SoPC Implementation of an AI generative encoding Hypercube-based NeuroEvolution of Augmented Topologies (HyperNEAT) with Hardware Accelerated Substrate.

B.Sc. in Electronic Industrial and Automation Engineering

Universitat de Girona (Spain) KU LEUVEN Technologie Campus (Belgium) 2019

Bachelor's Thesis: Integration of the control of HVAC and other home automation features through voice using Raspberry Pi and KNX communication in an educational "care case" that simulates a hypothetic home.

HarvardX: CS50's Introduction to Artificial Intelligence with Python

In Progress